Guide to the First Unitarian Church of Ithaca, New York records, 1861-1986.
First Unitarian Church of Ithaca, New York records, 1861-1986.
- Helverson, Ralph (bound), 1949-1953 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Helverson, Ralph (bound), 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Laypeople, 1950-1984 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Audio Tape Requests, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Weary, Gerald, 1959, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Werner, Ernest, 1962-1965 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Heizer, Cyrus (bound), 1915 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Services: Christenings and Dedications, 1964-1969 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Dedication Ceremonies and Forms Used, 1960s (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Funeral Pre-Planning, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Installation Services, 1925-1971 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Marriage Services and Guides, 1950s-1970s (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Membership Ceremony, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Memorial Services, 1968, 1972, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Orders of Service (September 17, 1922-June 10, 1923; June 8, 1924; May 21, 1939; October 16, 1940; December 20, 1942; April 25, 1943; September 26, 1943; December 12, 1943; December 26, 1943), 1924-1944 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Orders of Service, 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Orders of Service, 1945-1946 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Orders of Service, 1946-1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Orders of Service, 1947-1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Orders of Service, 1948-1953 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Orders of Service and Unitarian Publications (2 Vols. Bound), 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Orders of Service (April 1, 1956; May 20, 1956; September-December 1956) (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Orders of Service and Unitarian (14 volumes bound), 1956-1968 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Orders of Service, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Orders of Service, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Orders of Service, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Orders of Service, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Orders of Service, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Orders of Service, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Order of Celebration Explanations, September 1974 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Orders of Service, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Orders of Service, 1975-1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Orders of Service, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Orders of Service, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Orders of Service, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Orders of Service, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Orders of Service, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Orders of Service, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Orders of Service, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Orders of Service, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Orders of Service, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Orders of Service, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Ordination Service Of Saunders, William, October 22, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Sukkot Celebration, October 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Summer Service Questionnaires, 1970s (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Summer Services, 1981-1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Sunday Morning Set-Up, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Women's Alliance: Annual Reports, By-Laws, Minutes, 1921-1934 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Annual Reports, 1934-1951 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Annual Reports, 1951-1955 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Annual Reports - Minutes, 1956-1965 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Annual Reports - Minutes, 1965-1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Bazaar Reports (1942, 1946-1948, 1950-1955, 1957-1959), 1942-1959 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Bazaar, 1960-1966 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Bazaar, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Bazaar, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Bazaar Posters (3 On Top Of Folder), 1971, 1970s (Box 12)
- Art Start--Church, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Bazaar, 1970-1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- By-Laws, 1903-1965 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Directories and Programs, 1896-1979 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Discussion Series, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- History, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Memorial Hymnal Donations, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Minutes (bound), 1895-1899 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Minutes (bound), 1899-1901 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Minutes (bound), 1901-1904 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Minutes (bound), 1904-1910 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Minutes (bound), 1909-1911 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Minutes (bound), 1911-1913 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Minutes (bound), 1913-1915 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Minutes (bound), 1915-1922 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Minutes (bound), 1929-1937 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Minutes (bound), 1953-1960 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Miscellaneous Financial Transactions (1936, 1945, 1948-1954, 1962-1967), 1936-1967 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Notes Of Meetings, 1949-1961 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Presidents, 1901-1947 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Reading Circle Compositions (2 bound volumes), 1929, 1933 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Reading Circle Report, 1941-1942 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Reports Of Garments Made During World War I, 1918-1921 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Service Auction, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Service Auction, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Services and Hymnbook, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Share The Joy Fund, 1971-1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Treasurer's Book, 1899-1908 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Treasurer's Check Registers, 1955-1974 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Will Notices, 1912-1949 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Church Finances: Investment Fund Journals, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Investment Fund Journals, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Investment Fund Bank Statements, March 30, 1979-December 31, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Investment Fund Bank Statements, July 31, 1980-December 31 1982 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Investment Fund Journals, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Investment Fund Journals, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Investment Fund Journals, 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Investment Fund Bank Statements, March 31, 1983-June 29, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Investment Fund Bank Statements, July 31, 1984-June 28, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Investment Fund Journals, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Investment Fund Journals, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Parish House Renovation, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Endowment Fund Check Registers, 1964-1983 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Sermons: Werner, Ernest (7" reel tape), November 10, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Music: Organ Music (7" reel tape), November 10, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Sermons: Harrington, Donald S. (7" reel tape. Includes Order of Service), October 10, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Panel On Worship (7" reel tape. Includes Order of Service), December 4, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Werner, Ernest (7" reel tape, side 1), September 22, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Gilbert, Richard S. (7" reel tape, side 1), September 28, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Werner, Ernest (7" reel tape, side 2), October 6 and 13, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Mrs. Johnson at Central School (7" reel tape, side 1) (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Ross, Mina: Story of Union Organizing (7" reel tape, side 1), 1969? (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Smith, Mendon W. (7" reel tape. Includes Order Of Service), January 9, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Cope, Robert L. (7" reel tape. Includes Order Of Service), October 11, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Gilbert, Richard S. (7" reel tape) (May 1, Feb. 20, and May 8, 1966) (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Freeman, Dr. Frank (7" reel tape) (Includes Order Of Service), May 14, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Werner, Ernest (7" reel tape) (Includes Order Of Service), December 1, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Weary, Gerald (7" reel tape) (Includes Order Of Service), May 7, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Publications: Unitarian, September 1, 1985-June 22, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)